JEAN CARLO MACHADO

SOFTWARE ENGINEER, TEAM LEADER, TEACHER

contato@jeancarlomachado.com.br

+55 (47) 99192-6677

2014-2018

PHPeste 2017: All about clean

Profile Create and maintain software that improve the world using science and open-source. Skills **Project Leadership** Systems Infrastructure development Ability to lead software Creating and managing teams observing delivery infrastructures of software Software Craftsman with efficiency, quality, and using Linux containers and experience in many team well being. clusters programming languages.

Unix/Linux Clean Code TDD **Technical**

C / C++ Docker Swarm / Kubernetes Optimization Techniques PHP Complexity Analysis GPU programming Python Elm

Experience

CompuFácil

CTO, Lead Engineer, Developer

Responsible for all technological aspects of the product. Hiring developers. Building clusters, building continuous integration and delivery, programming

Tempo Real Eventos

Git Teacher 2016-2017

Teaching the basics as well as the advanced and internal data-structures of git for many audiences.

CUB

2012-2014 **Backend Engineer**

Webapps, and e-commerces development, servers management.

NAPNE

2011-2012 Scholarship

Developing accessibility hardware with Microchip's processors.

git/git Doctrine Openphp-src php-unit pdepend vim/vim source torvalds/linux

FISL 17: Introduction to Rust PHPeste 2016: All about clean Lectures

code code PHPConference 2017: Advanced PHPConference 2017: Functional

Git for Devs PHP beyond array_map

Education

UDESC - Joinville, SC

Classes in Master's in Applied Computing 2016-2017

Special student with focus on HPC Optimization

IFRS - Bento Gonçalves, RS

Analysis and Development of Systems 2010-2015

Higher education in Analysis and Development of Systems

SENAI - Garibaldi, RS

Eletronics 2009-2010

Technical degree in electronics